{"name":"Game","timeLimitInSeconds":60,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":10,"questions":[{"questionText":"What was the API we used to write javascript web apps?","answers":[{"answerText":"MongoDB","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"NodeJS","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Notepad++","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Windows Movie Maker","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the API we used to create databases?","answers":[{"answerText":"Express","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Cookie-Parser","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"MongoDB","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What is Scott Lambert's real first name?","answers":[{"answerText":"Scott","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Ronald","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Lambert","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How do we launch our Javascript apps?","answers":[{"answerText":"Command Prompt","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Double click on it","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Visual Studio Debugging","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Windows Movie Maker again","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What port did we host most of the apps on","answers":[{"answerText":"5560","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"3001","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"27017","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"8550","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"3000","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What library did we use to connect our apps to Unity?","answers":[{"answerText":"DocketIO","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"SocketIO","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"PocketIO","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"RocketIO","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How many holes does a straw have?","answers":[{"answerText":"One","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Two","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What port were our databases on?","answers":[{"answerText":"3232","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"71072","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"8","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"27017","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"12345","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Windows Movie Maker?","answers":[{"answerText":"Yes","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"No","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which of the following is correct?","answers":[{"answerText":"Soccer","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Football","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Futbol","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"FUUUUUTBOOOOL","isCorrect":true}]}]}